amylynnandrews.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Amy Lynn Andrews

Privacy is good. I like it and I assume you do too. As a reader of mine, your privacy is important to me. 

### The Chips and Salsa Version

This site uses cookies, pixels and code to track your activity here. This is common practice on the internet. If you don’t want your computer activity to be tracked in this way, please exit the site now.

Tracked activity includes, but is not limited to, pages you visit, links you click, blog comments you leave and email subscriptions forms you fill out and submit.

Information that is collected includes, but is not limited to, your name & email address (in the case of email subscription), IP address and browser information.

I may provide personal information to an applicable third party in order to provide services such as Facebook to target Facebook Ads and Mad Mimi to manage email subscriptions.

You can decline to submit personal information at any time. If you decline, I may not be able to provide service to you.

You may request deletion of your personal information by sending an email to amy@amylynnandrews.com.

I will never sell your personal information.

There may be third party advertisers and companies which utilize cookies to provide advertisements that would most interest you. I have no control over these cookies. This is not unique to my site, but is common across the internet.

Your IP address and other information (such as the day and time of your visit) is tracked for the purpose of understanding trends and helping me provide information that is most relevant and helpful. Again, this is not unique to this site, but is common practice across the internet.

On AmyLynnAndrews.com you’ll find a lot of links to other sites, over which I have no control, nor do I have control over the privacy policies of those sites. Policies of other sites may differ from mine.

### The Whole Enchilada Version

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which AmyLynnAndrews.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [https://amylynnandrews.com](https://amylynnandrews.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by AmyLynnAndrews.com.

**Personal identification information**

This site collects personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

This site uses “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

AmyLynnAndrews.com collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve our Site.  _We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To process transactions.  _We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _To send periodic emails.  _The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

**Changes to this privacy policy**

AmyLynnAndrews.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting me**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact me at:

AmyLynnAndrews@gmail.com

This document was last updated on May 25, 2018.
